<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="hello">This is a test application to evaluate the positioning capabilities of Android.</string>
    <string name="app_name">LocPairs</string>
   	<string name="addtab_name">Add Server</string>
	<string name="searchtab_name">Find WFS</string>
	<string name="contab_name">Connections</string>
	<string name="search_prompt_radius">Max radius</string>
	<string name="search_prompt_results">Max results</string>
	<string name="no_wfs">No servers to display</string>
	
	<!-- LocPairs -->
	<string name="description_logo">LocPairs</string>
	<string name="menu">LocPairs Menu</string>
	<string name="btn_settings">Settings</string>
	<string name="map_settings">Map Settings</string>
	<string name="btn_instructions">Instructions</string>
	<string name="btn_lobby">Lobby</string>
	<string name="settings_title">Settings</string>
	<string name="btn_scan">Scan QR Code</string>
	<string-array name="LobbyUserArray">
		<item>UserName1</item>
		<item>UserName2</item>
		<item>UserName3</item>
		<item>UserName4</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="description_refresh">refresh</string>
	<string name="description_chat">chat</string>
	<string name="next_round">Next Round</string>
	<string name="instructions01">Welcome to LocPairs. If you don’t know how to play this game read the instructions below.
		But before you can play the game, you need to install the MXA manager and a Barcode scanner. You have to set the values 
		in the MXA Manager to host: 141.30.203.90, port: 5222 and your name and password from your XMPP login.</string>
	<string name="instructions02">LocPairs is based on the classic pairs game, but you can play it in a whole building.
		In the LocPairs game there are 32 cards placed behind several doors of a building. 
		The teams take turns flipping pairs of cards over. On each turn, one member of the teams will first turn 
		one card over and then the second member of the team will turn a second card. 
		If the two cards match, the team scores one point, the two cards are removed from the game, 
		and the team gets another turn. If they do not match, the cards are turned back over and the next team 
		can uncover two cards.</string>
	<string name="instructions03">The cards can be turned over by walking to a door that is marked on the map. 
		There you find a QR-code that you have to scan with your mobile device. But you only have 30 seconds time. 
		When the time is up without turning over a card the next team has its turn.</string>
	<string name="instructions04">
		The goal is to match more pairs of cards than the opposing teams. When cards are turned over, 
		it is important to remember where they are for when the matching card is turned up later in the game.</string>
	<string name="instructions05">How to start a game? First you have to join a game by clicking the lobby button. 
		There you will see the other players who are interested in the game. You play LocPairs in teams of two players. 
		These teams will be set automatically. To start a game you need an even number of players and at least four players. 
		When each player has clicked the ready button the game starts. You see the outline of the building you are in. 
		You can see the movement of you and your team mate on the card. You also can see the location of the other players. 
		On the bottom of the display the count down is placed.</string>
	<string name="instructions06"> There is also a special feature. If your team mate is not sure behind witch door the matching card is you 
		can show it to him by pointing on it in the map. Only your partner can see it and is able to choose the 
		right door even if you are in different parts of the building.</string>
	<string name="instructions07">If you will end the game or your connection to the server breaks down your game will be quit. 
		At the same time your partner gets the information that you left the game and is forced to end it too. 
		The other players can continue the game.</string>
</resources>
